Uh Uh Too Spicy
You want my A to the Z
But you won’t 어림없지
맞혀봐 Sweet 또는 Freak
What’s hiding underneath (I see)
망설이듯 간 보는 너 기회는 없어 Oh
Nah You won’t get it
No No, You won’t get it
I say
깜빡 한순간 끌어당겨 You’ll be mine (Mine)
살짝 다가와 Can cross my borderline (Line Line Line)
널 따분하게 했던 Every day
흥미로운 덫을 던져줄게
뛰어들어 봐
Just right now
'Cause I’m too Spicy for your heart
Ring the fire alarm
심장을 파고들어 넌
I'm too Spicy
번지는 자극 속에 넌
바로 그 순간
또 다른 나를 발견해
I’m too Spicy too too
I’m too Spicy
Don’t Stop 겁내지 마
Bang Bang 외쳐봐
I’m too Spicy Yeah I’m too Spicy
You know that I
Don’t Stop 용기 내 봐
Next step, Myself
I’m too Spicy
Too Spicy too too
Tell me what you see
When you look at me
'Cause I am a 10 out of 10 honestly
기세가 다른 Move
널 압도하는 Groove
But you keep wasting your time Dude
Don't chase me 경고해 난
Erase me 멀리 달아나
Hey 이젠 알겠니
원래부터 Bad I’m so bad honestly
So bad
전부 가질래 지금부턴 Call you mine (Mine)
도망칠 거면 Don’t cross my borderline (Line Line Line)
늘 뻔하기만 했던 Every day
이제 그만 Rule을 벗어날 때
어렵지 않아
Just right now
'Cause I’m too Spicy for your heart
Ring the fire alarm
심장을 파고들어 넌
I'm too Spicy
번지는 자극 속에 넌
바로 그 순간
또 다른 나를 발견해
I’m too Spicy too too
I’m too Spicy
Ready? Uh
좀 더 강도를 높여 다음다음다음
One of a kind
우린 한계를 앞서 Wow Wow Wow
That’s Right
'Cause I’m too Spicy for your heart
Ring the fire alarm
새로운 도전 끝에 넌
I'm too Spicy
변화할 시간이야 넌
지금 이 순간
또 다른 나를 찾아내
I’m too Spicy too too
I’m too Spicy
Don’t Stop 겁내지 마
Bang Bang 외쳐봐
I’m too Spicy Yeah I’m too Spicy
You know that I
Don’t Stop 용기 내 봐
Next step, Myself
I’m too Spicy I’m too Spicy
I’m too Spicy too too I’m too Spicy
'Cause I
Oh Yeah
Yeah I’m too Spicy for your heart
(Yeah I’m too Spicy for your heart)
마침내 번져오는 Joy (Enjoy joy joy joy)
Yeah I’m too Spicy for your heart
I’m too Spicy too too
I’m too Spicy
For you